Lukasz Zatyka

<u>linkedin.com/in/lukasz-zatyka</u> lukasz.zatyka@gmail.com • +48881718466

I am a Frontend Development specialist with a background in management,

About me: I am confident and clear in my thoughts, possessing strong communication and presentation skills. I strive to excel in software development by focusing on user experience and upholding best practices in programming frontend sites.

Personality type: INFJ-A

Specialties: Web Technologies, Negotiation & Business Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CodiLime • 05/2021 - Present

Frontend Engineer

- I have the pleasure of being part of a fantastic team, working together to transform ideas into a final product ready for launch in the market, specifically in network engineering services (SDN, SD-WAN, Cloud).
- · Responsibilities:
- Creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces by utilizing design systems, charts, and frameworks to construct a network monitoring and intelligence platform.
- Developing and documenting reusable UI components with Storybook, which can be easily shared across projects.
- Consuming API, delivering features, and creating interactive interfaces for both mobile and desktop devices.

PKP Informatyka spółka z o.o. • Warsaw, Mazowieckie, Poland • 01/2020 - 05/2021

Frontend Developer

- Aim: Cooperation in design and creation a new version of web application Bilkom.pl
- · Tech Stack: React.js, Redux, Storybook, Material UI, CSS in JS, Git, Figma, Adobe, Atlassian

Reall Sp. z o.o. • Warsaw, Masovian District, Poland • 04/2019 - 09/2019

Frontend Developer

- · Gaining web developer experiences as an agile team member in the start-up
- web application which helps the elder generation to lead an active and fulfilled
- life. Working in Google for Startups acceleration program.
- · Responsibilities:
- UX/ UI prototypes (Adobe Xd / Photoshop / Illustrator / InVision)
- Programming (Vue.js, Node.js, HTML/SCSS, Bootstrap, Git)
- · Supporting company operations and strategy

CRI Sp. z.o.o. • Poland • 10/2017 - 03/2019

Solution Owner

Leading project to implement digital transformation (a mix of digital technologies)

- · System administration and users support at ERP Comarch Optima (MSSQL, SAP
- · Crystal Reports)
- · Administration of the company's database server (SQL Server 2012, Comarch, Płatnik
- · ZUS, dGCS)
- · Preparation and implementation of documents regarding the protection of personal
- data (GDPR)

Project Manager

- Managing quality control projects in teams of 50-150 people (ISO 9001, Lean, Kanban)
- · Responsibility for achieving goals: timeliness, budget, efficiency

Najlepsze Wakacje • Warsaw, Masovian District, Poland • 01/2009 - 05/2017 Web Developer / Graphic Designer

- Designing and leading digital projects www.najlepszewakacje.pl (UX, UI, HTML/CSS)
- Developing an e-commerce application www.pogotowieurlopowe.pl (UI, HTML/CSS)
- Creating and coding effective newsletters (HTML/CSS, Photoshop & Illustrator)
- Creating effective marketing campaigns (SEM, AdWords, GDN, FacebookAds)
- Designing various graphics (logos, newsletters, banners, landing pages, and other
- promotions)
- Technologies and frameworks: MySQL, Apache, PHP, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, HTML/CSS
- · CMS: Drupal, WordPress
- · Analytic panels: Google Ads, Google Analytics, Google Search Console, FB Ads,
- · Tools: Trello, Git, npm, Gulp, InVision, GSuite
- Graphic: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

Co-Owner

- Being responsible for the sales process and digital development (contracts with
- service providers, tool selection, office design and equipment)

Obnum • Warsaw, Masovian District, Poland • 02/2007 - 01/2009

Project Engineer

- Programming CNC (numerical machines) using G-code
- · Designing new products and creating their visual identity

Worktech. • Warszawa, woj. mazowieckie, Polska • 01/2003 - 02/2007

Junior Engineering Technologist / CNC Programmer

- Programming CNC (numerical machines) using G-code
- · Design and development molds for injection and blow molding using CAx
- · Create and update product documentation drawings and specifications

EDUCATION

Engineer's degree in Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering

Warsaw University of Technology • 01/2005 - 01/2009

Kanban for Design and Innovation

Kanban University • 06/2022 - Present

AgilePM® Foundation

APMG International • 11/2018 - Present

The Digital Garage

Google • 03/2017 - Present

The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People

FranklinCovey • 03/2013 - Present

PROJECTS

CrispTime.com

Reall Sp. z o.o. • 04/2019 - 04/2020

CrispTime is a social media platform. With CrispTime, you can develop your passions, gain experience and share your knowledge with others. CrispTime connects active people who want to collaborate and realize their ideas. Tech stack: Node.js, Vue.js, GCP, RethingDB, Git, npm Design stack: Xd Adobe, Photoshop, Illustrator, InVision Team stack: Slack, GSuite, ClickUp

Najlepszewakacje.pl

01/2007 - 03/2017

e-catalogue with premium hotels Tech stack: MySQL, Drupal (6-8), Bootstrap (3-4), Javascript, Ajax, jQuery, API Rests

Pogotowieurlopowe.pl

01/2014 - 03/2017

Search page with holiday offers and on-line booking

Konstancinochronka.pl

charity work

SKILLS

Business Strategy, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), ERP Software, Git, Google Cloud Platform (GCP), JavaScript, Material-Ul, Microsoft SQL Server, MobX, Negotiation, New Business Development, Next.js, Node.js, Project Management, Project Planning, React.js, Redux, Storybook, TypeScript, Vue.js